Hello and Welcome back. I am going to show you now an example of
【未完成版本】欢迎大家回来 现在我要为大家演示
imaging painting inside Adobe Photoshop. Adobe has implemented a number of types
一个Adobe Photoshop内图像修复的例子 Adobe有各种类型的
of image in painting algorithms. Some are based on partial differential
图像修复算法工具 其中一些正是基于
equations of the type that we showed in the previous videos.
我们在之前的视频中介绍过的 偏微分方程 的类型
Actually, they used a higher order partial differential equation as we have
实际上 它们采用了高阶偏微分方程
seen in one of the videos in this class. And also, they have implemented this
我们在这节课的视频中 已经看到过 除此之外
smart cut and paste type of techniques that we show in the previous video.
其中还应用了 在前面的视频中也已经演示过的 智能剪切和粘贴技术
So let's see an example. In particular, we are using the tool that
现在我们来看这个例子 我们使用的这个工具叫做
is called the Healing Brush, and it has a number of options, as I just
修复笔刷 如我之前所说 它有好几种选项
described. Some based on partial differential
其中一些基于偏微分方程
equation, some based on cut and paste. And what we see here is one of the images
一些基于剪切和粘贴 在这里我们看到的是
they show in the previous video, this was the image to be in painted, we
之前视频中出现过的一幅图像 这就是需要修复的图像
want to remove this object. This is the result that they show in the
我们想要去除掉这个物体 这幅是前面视频中展示过的处理结果
previous video. It was not obtained with Photoshop.
这并不是通过Photoshop处理得到的
It was obtained with similar techniques of smart cut and paste and variation and
而是用相似的智能剪切和粘贴技术 加上一些变换和公式
formulations. So, lets see how we can apply the Healing
【未完成版本】现在来看看我们如何应用修复笔刷工具
Brush. Now, in real time in the demo, to obtain
在这个实时演示中 来获得
similar results of removing this. So, the basic idea, I hope you can see
相似的去除效果 基本思想是我希望大家能够
the circle there. Let me just put it in a nice background,
看到这里的这个圆圈 让我把它移到一个清楚的背景上
so you can see it. And the basic idea, is you kind of start
现在大家可以看到了 然后在想要去除的目标上
painting what you want to be removed. I'm going to release now, and in
进行涂抹 接着松开鼠标
thinking, and it's gone. It's basically gone, and it's kind of the
稍等一会儿 它就不见了 然后背景似乎开始出现了
background starts to appear. We'll just do a bit more.
下面我们再接着多去除一点
I paint around, I brush, and is working, and is disappearing,
我在周围用笔刷涂抹 运行 然后消失了
and is starting to look like this. Again, remember this was not the
图像开始看起来像这幅了 记住这并不是原始图像
original. This was [INAUDIBLE] by the techniques we
这是被我们讲过的技术 修复出来的
describe and now is happening in real time.
现在实时地展现给了大家
Let me just do one more. And you see, it's starting to disappear.
让我再来刷一次 大家可以看到 它开始消失了
And it's very nicely [INAUDIBLE] filled in.
非常漂亮地除去掉了这一块
And we can keep going until we make everything that we don't want, every
我们可以接着这样 直到我们去除了
object that we don't want, we make it disappear by basically
所有不想要的东西 我们通过
blending information from the background inside it.
将背景的信息融合到它里面去 来使它消失了
So, this is a nice demo of something that is available with Photoshop.
以上就是一个采用Photoshop功能修复图像的演示
Thank you very much. I see you in the next video.
【未完成版本】谢谢大家 下一个视频再见